An item that can cure all diseases, huh?
With it, maybe I could cure
Mom's Eternal Sleep Disease.
The Elixir of Life has three ingredients...
I don't have any of them,
but it's obvious where they are.
That said, it'd be suicide to enter
that castle without getting stronger.
I need to level up more...
I need to get stronger.
You accept, then?!
Things have changed on my end.
I'm willing to join you on the nineteen
C-Rank raids you mentioned.
Yes!
Under one condition, though.
Sure! Whatever you want!
You and I will be going in alone.
As in... You and I would be the only ones
clearing the C-Rank dungeon, Boss?
That's right.
But C-Rank gates require a minimum
of eight team members to enter.
So we hire people to meet the quota.
The same way Hwang Dongsuk did.
I-Isn't that... kind of risky?
Think about it this way...
If it's just the two of us, we can clear
these nineteen raids with no casualties.
A strike team capable of handling
nineteen operations with zero injuries—
wouldn't that be the perfect thing
to impress your dad with?
I get you.
Let's do it, Boss!
I'll arrange the extra members and the gates!
And how can I help you?
Impressive. But I'd expect nothing less
from an S-Rank hunter.
I was waiting for the right moment
to approach you...
I hope you'll excuse the
interruption to your training.
Here is my card.
It's been over a decade
since the gates appeared,
and the world's changed at
a dizzying pace since then.
Infrastructure, the economy,
the media, even politics...
The dungeons have changed all those things.
In particular, our infrastructure,
the foundation of everyone's lives,
can no longer operate without
the resources from dungeons.
And hunters are the only ones capable of
retrieving these vital resources for our world.
Those hunters are in turn overseen by
the Hunter's Association,
a public institution.
The Association takes awakened
hunters, grades them for rank,
registers them, and handles oversight.
They manage the gates
that don't go to auction,
as well as deal with dungeon breaks.
But the Association is nothing more
than a function of the state.
The vast majority of those vital resources
from dungeons are collected by
the guilds: the businesses who
hire out hunters as a service.
The guilds have become extremely wealthy
from the dungeon resources they collect.
Among them, the Hunters Guild,
the White Tiger Guild, the Reaper Guild,
the Fame Guild, and the Knights Guild
are the largest five guilds in the country.
They have a functional monopoly
on dungeon-related profits.
And I see no reason to sit back
and simply let that continue.
Especially considering how important
these resources are to everyday life.
Leaving their collection to a group
of mercenaries is out of the question.
We've contributed so much to this country.
It's our responsibility to handle this, as well.
And the establishment of this guild
is crucial to our accomplishing that.
Y-Yes, sir.
Even if that's true,
there's a lot of risk involved
in recruiting an S-Rank hunter to act
as my brother's business partner...
Which isn't the case for me.
Looks like anything extra I do
isn't counted anymore.
It seems that cursed random loot box
that was offered in the secret quest
is out of my reach now.
I had hoped for an item as valuable
as the key to the Demon's Castle...
Wait. There's still the chance that
the regular random loot box
could have a key to something like
the instance dungeon from before...
Or not.
With my stats as high as they are now,
three points aren't enough
to make a real change anymore.
I'd like to level up more efficiently,
but I have to wait on Jinho
for the C-Rank dungeons.
Wait, the penalty zone!
Maybe if I fight that centipede...
No. I might have an easier time
running now, but beating it...?
And there's no guarantee
I'd get any experience points.
They need hunters for a D-Rank gate?
The Hunter's Association
is forming a strike team...
which means I wouldn't be
able to fight on my own.
Should I say no?
But I guess it's better than nothing.
This is frustrating.
I didn't stand a chance against you, Master.
I'm just not ready to be
beaten yet. That's all.
It's a shame, though. I wish I could've
fought you at your best...
Still worried about that?
It's been months since I lost my arm.
An emergency summons?
Low-ranked hunters get a lot of calls
for what amounts to running errands.
You seriously won't consider retiring, Master?
Retirement?
You've got a point. An old man with one arm
missing might not be of much help at all.
That's not what I meant, sir!
Still, I may have lost an arm, but I survived.
My best years are already behind me,
but I'd like to spend what I have left
contributing to society.
Looks like I've got my next raid.
Say, honey...
Isn't it about time you considered
something other than hunting?
We're talking about this again?
But it's so dangerous. All those people
died in the raid from before,
and you only barely survived, right?
Well, yeah...
Daddy! Up!
The thing is, Eunji is starting
preschool next year,
and Eunha will be in middle school.
We need the money, don't we?
That might be true, but...
It'll be fine. The Association doesn't send
low-ranked hunters into dangerous dungeons.
The other time was just an exception.
You're right. I'm sorry
for making such a fuss.
Don't worry about it.
Be careful, okay?
You bet! I love you.
Daddy?
Yeah? What's up?
Daddy, are you strong?
You bet I am!
I can beat scary monsters, y'know!
Wow! You really are strong!
You've got some damn nerve.
What are you talking about?
I can't believe you stuck me with
that interview. It was a waste of time.
I managed to catch it.
You made a good impression.
I found your answers to be quite profound.
I'm not here for a bunch of empty flattery!
And I'm pretty sure the interview was
meant to be for you in the first place!
Well, considering the offer
made to Chairman Go
was for a talented hunter of great character
who is dedicated to the job...
I mean, does that really sound like me?
Well, at least you realize
how sketchy you are.
Whatever! So, what's this about, anyway?
There's no way you asked me to come over
just so I could chew you out.
There was something
I thought you should know...
Yoojin Construction are getting ready
to launch their own guild.
I know. They've been trying
to make moves in secret.
There's been rumors about
headhunting at my guild.
I suppose if you already know,
then I wasted your time.
And I already know that you knew I knew.
Can we please cut the crap?
I'll ask you one more time.
What's this really about?
You haven't called much lately.
Is everything goin' okay?
Yeah.
How 'bout work?
Well... fine.
You've always been such a scaredy-cat.
Are you really handlin' being a hunter?
You're B-Rank, right? I'm sure most folks
would be pretty strong in that case,
but wouldn't you just be gettin' in the way?
You should come back home
an' help out with the business.
Your Pa's worried—
Quit trying to run my life!
I can make my own decisions!
So just drop it!
What are you—
I'm just in the way...?
But...
I wanna try a little more.
Excuse me.
How can I help you, Hunter Cha Hae-in?
While I was training, I was approached
by a scout from Yoojin Construction.
I thought you should know.
They're apparently launching a new guild
and wanted me to join them as guild master.
And I assume, since you're telling me this,
that you turned them down?
Right. I refused the offer.
That's a relief. Thank you for telling me.
It's nothing. I was wondering...
I saw President Baek on my way in.
What were you talking about?
What do you think about Jeju Island?
Jeju Island? Why do you ask?
Since the failed raid,
the island has been sealed off,
with only occasional reconnaissance
done from the shore.
And the public receives a single
annual update about any changes.
People are trying to forget about the island—
and the terror it represents.
Yeah, but can you blame them?
Except, no matter how commonplace
gates may have become,
or how much I get fawned over as
the "ultimate weapon" of humanity,
I can never forget about that island,
or what happened there.
I intend on clearing that island
in the near future.
And to do that, I need you
and the others on the same page.
We must gain strength, gather allies,
and sway public opinion.
That's why you arranged for the interview
and are training new hunters.
Isn't there something you left
behind on that island, as well?
Eunseok... Byung-gu...
Please. I'm begging you...
They have to die.
I'm heading out.
It's a holiday, but you've got work again?
You keep busy lately.
I guess.
Hard to believe you're the same guy
who had to take time off to recover
from his injuries after every gate.
All the training pay off?
Probably. In any case, I'm able
to make a steady living now.
That's a good thing, right?
I guess it is.
Wait, Jinwoo! What about your stuff?
It'll be fine. I'm heading out.
Wait, hang on...
It's not like you're making
a quick trip to the store.
I didn't awaken to a physical power,
which means my sword
is useless against magic beasts.
The martial arts I've spent decades on
are useless inside of a dungeon.
A swordsman like myself gaining magic-focused
powers is quite the twist of fate.
But I'm sure there's a reason for it.
Are you...?
Mr. Song?
I wasn't sure it was you, but it is! Sung!
It's been a while.
I never thought I'd run into you
in a place like this!
I must say, where'd that
gentle-looking boy go?
How have you changed so much
in just a few months?
Plus...
Didn't you lose a leg?
When I woke up in the hospital, it was back.
I see!
There must've been a high-ranked healer
among the hunters who came to collect you!
Whatever the case, it's a relief seeing
a young man like yourself has fully healed.
That's nice of you to say.
But, Mr. Song, your arm...
Too much time had passed
since my injury, I'm afraid.
I don't mind, though.
You know, someone from the Association
had told me you were alive.
It's so good to see you!
What are you doing here, anyway, Mr. Song?
Answering a summons from the Association.
It's supposed to be urgent.
You, too?
What a coincidence.
This is quite the reunion.
Jinwoo?
Joohee...
Along with... Mr. Kim and Mr. Kang.
It's only natural.
We sacrificed Sung in order
to escape on that day.
And I can't blame Kim for being too ashamed
to face me, after what he did.
That said... five survivors from
that tragedy have been reunited.
In that case...
It really is you, isn't it, Jinwoo?
You look like a whole different person!
Yeah. It's been a while.
You're so much taller,
and your leg is healed...
I guess you were fine
after I visited you, after all.
You visited me?
Nice! We got a fine little lady in this group.
What's up, baby? You and this guy an item?
You should play with us—
Shut your mouths.
This outing isn't for recreation.
I'll now brief our regular hunters,
if you'd come this way.
What's going on here...?
These men are the prisoner substitute
hunters who will be joining you today.
Substitute hunters?! We're supposed
to fight alongside criminals?!
They are hunter convicts, but they're
here to reduce their sentences
and are unlikely to cause trouble.
We're short-staffed due to a exodus
of local hunters. I hope you'll understand.
What a mess...
You'll be accompanied by an overseer from
the Hunter's Association, Kang Taeshik, too.
He's B-Rank, so even in
the worst-case scenario,
he should be able to handle
three C-Rank criminals with ease.
Please, rest assured.
I don't know if this is a good idea.
You should sit the raid out, Joohee.
What about you, Jinwoo?
I'm going.
Then I am, too.
I understand.
Damn, it's good to be free.
We're not slaves here, man.
Is this kinda thing allowed?
Shut up. You're convicts.
You know what happens if you act up, right?
I'm Kang Taeshik, an inspector with the
Hunter's Association Surveillance Team.
I'll be responsible for them,
so you can relax.
Who's going to take point on the raid today?
Sung... Do you mind if I lead?
No, go ahead.
Thank you for giving me this chance.
M-Mr. Song?
On that day, seven people died because of me.
The magnitude of my failure to protect
everyone can not be understated.
But... six of us did survive, because of you.
So let me say this, as a
representative of the others:
I am so grateful to you.
You don't have to bow, Mr. Song.
Is it all right with you, as well, Kim?
Go ahead.
Well, with that being the case,
I will take point in the dungeon.
Understood. Let's get underway, then.
Off we go, now...
Into the dungeon.